## **GAVIN SWOFFORD**

## SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

## **Contact Details**

(615) 406 8005 GavinSwofford@gmail.com github.com/Swoffm Ilinkedin.com/in/gavin-swofford/

#### **Personal Profile**

I started to have a passion for computer programming when I started my first internship. I love learning new things, and solving challenging problems. I graduated from Trevecca in May 2020 with a Bachelors of Business Administration with a concentration in Information Technology and a minor in Specialized Computing. Before graduating I spoke with an old employer about my future. It became clear that I was not finished with schooling and the wisest plan of action would be to attend a software school. I am currently attending Nashville Software School until November 2020 studying full stack web development.

## Skills

- JavaScript
- HTML
- CSS
- React
- Git
- C# .Net
- SQL
- Visual Studio Code
- Visual Studio
- Processing
- Oracle
- Python
- Keras
- Nelas
- GitHub
- Agile Software Development

# Captstone Project Fossil Hunt Project Goals

- Give Fossil Collectors a place to communicate with other collectors.
- Give Fossil Collectors the ability to catalog their collection

## Technologies

JavaScript | React | HTML | CSS | Git | GitHub | VS Code

## LSTM RNN Academic Project Stock Predictor

## **Project Goals**

- Utilize a stock API
- Learn more about how LSTM RNN's work
- Utilize Machine Learning to predict future stock prices

#### Technologies

Python | AlphaVantage API | Keras | Matplot Lib | Anaconda | Spyder

## **Work Experience**

## **Application Developer Intern**National General

05/2019-08/2019

- Worked on the company's AI team
- Analyzed data for team members
- Learned how to use Google's natural language understanding platform, Dialogflow
- Worked along side team members to test software for bugs
- Had opportunity to build mock features in the App

### Technologies

Dialogflow | Basic SQL | Excel | Visual Studio

## **Web Developer Intern**

**National General** 

06/2017-08/2017

- Assisted in creating various web pages.
- Worked with HTML and CSS in Visual Studio
- Implement Bootstrap into various web pages

## Technologies

CSHTML | Bootstrap | Visual Studio | HTML

#### Education

## Full Stack Web Development Nashville Software School

o5/2020-PRESENT

A full time six month software development program learning full-stack technologies through the creation of software applications in group and individual settings.

## Technologies

HTML | CSS | SQL | C# .Net | ADO.Net | Git | GitHub | JavaScript | React | Visual Studio | VS Code

### BA: IT

#### **Trevecca Nazarene University**

08/2016-05/2020

Business Admin, Minor Specialized Computing